&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果你对打字稿和流程感兴趣，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you're curious about TypeScript and Flow and
他们的不同之处，这既有相似之处，也有不同之处，但是
their differences, this is both similarities and differences, but
特别是差异，我发现这篇特别的文章非常有帮助。
especially differences, I found this particular article to be very helpful.
他们基本上肩并肩地完成了两个项目，
They went through essentially both projects side by side,
一大串不同的特征和
big long list of all the different characteristics and
在哪里他们是相同的，在哪里他们是不同的。
where they are the same, same, same, same, and the places where they are different.
这是一篇很好的文章，所以我建议你去看看。
It's a good article, so I'd recommend checking it out.
总之，我想说的是，类型脚本和流程在以下方面非常有用
In summary, what I would say is that TypeScript and flow are very useful in
很多人发现它们对解决他们的打字问题很有帮助，
that a lot of people are finding them to be helpful to solve their typing issues,
有助于使它们的类型更加明显。
helpful to make their types more obvious.
我发现他们令人沮丧，或者可能只是我感到沮丧
Where I find them to be frustrating or maybe it's just me frustrated about
生态系统是我们似乎立即跳到的，这是唯一的选择。
the ecosystem is that we seem to jump immediately to, that's the only option.
如果有类型，则可以完全忽略类型并使用三重等于，或者
If you have types, you can either ignore types entirely and use triple equals, or
你可以跳到另一个极端，
you can jump to this other extreme,
它是JavaScript之上的一层，
which is layer on something on top of JavaScript,
我认为这根本不是JavaScript的DNA。
which I would argue is fundamentally not really the DNA of JavaScript.
我希望在两者之间有一些东西。
And I would like for there to be something in between.